<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Josh Stepp</title>
    <link>https://joshstepp.com/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Josh Stepp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016-2019. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://joshstepp.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Western Governors University: Master of Science Cybersecurity and Information Assurance (MSCSIA) - My Review</title>
      <link>https://joshstepp.com/post/wgumscsia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshstepp.com/post/wgumscsia/</guid>
      <description>Before I begin, I would like you to take note of the date in which this was published. If you are reading this in the future, there is a good chance some of this may change. I am attempting to make this post as evergreen as possible, just as precaution, your mileage may vary.
So, for the past six months or so, I have been plugging away at the Western Governors University Master of Science, Cybersecurity and Information Assurance program during all my free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Lab Part II : My Setup</title>
      <link>https://joshstepp.com/post/homelabpt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshstepp.com/post/homelabpt2/</guid>
      <description>My Homelab is a work horse for me; I use it to train smaller machine learning (tensorflow) models on, mess around with Starcraft AI bots on it, along with doing Information Security research and some light malware analysis/ reverse engineering. Essentially, it is a jack-of-all trades, master of none type of workstation.
Going in I had the following requirements:
 CHEAP… I want this to be under $300USD (not counting the GPU)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Lab Part I : Approaches and Why</title>
      <link>https://joshstepp.com/post/homelabpt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshstepp.com/post/homelabpt1/</guid>
      <description>This will be a multiple part post outlining my opinions of homelabs and what you should consider when building your lab. I will also include a few resources I can vouch for and have used. Furthermore, I do not claim to have all the answers and your setup/needs will be different from mine. That being said, I will start off in a general sense and narrow done as these posts go on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pelican to GOpher: Migrating my Blog to the Hugo Framework</title>
      <link>https://joshstepp.com/post/migratetohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshstepp.com/post/migratetohugo/</guid>
      <description>If you have been to this site recently, you will have noticed that it doesn’t look the same. I have migrated from Pelican, a static site generator written in Python to Hugo, a static site generator written in Go (golang).
Why? My old blog just wasn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. The Pelican project updated and when I tried to migrate my local project from one computer to another with different versions I broke the site, which in turn went nuclear on my github repo for the project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>